PhraseID	EN
SV_agiH80KLEHczslo	
QID4_QuestionText	Please select the option that best represents you
QID4_Choice1	I am a parent/guardian/older relative of a child that I have helped care for in some capacity and that child plays Roblox
QID4_Choice2	I am a parent/guardian/older relative of a child that I have helped care for in some capacity and that child plays Roblox
QID4_Choice3	I am a person
QID118_QuestionText	Exempt Information Sheet<br><br>&nbsp;Dr.Imani Munyaka, [add your name] are conducting this research and asking for your consent to participate. This section provides a summary of important information. The rest of the form provides additional details.<br><br>&nbsp;The purpose of this study is to gather feedback about Roblox from gamer parents. You will complete a survey and demographic questionnaire. Communicating with us (optional) and responding to our survey will take approximately 15 minutes. There may or may not be any direct benefit to you from participating in this study. You may think deeply about your identity. The investigator, however, may learn more about practitioner beliefs.<br><br>➘➘Your participation in this study is completely voluntary and you can withdraw at any time. Choosing not to participate or withdrawing will result in no penalty or loss of benefits to which you are entitled. You are free to skip any question that you choose.➘➘By participating in this research you are indicating that you are at least 18 years old, U.S .Resident, have read this consent form, and agree to participate in this research study.<br><br>&nbsp;Please keep this consent form for your records. <br><br>After reviewing this form, if you have any questions about the study please email one of the study personnel (designstudyresearchers@gmail.com) or Dr. Imani Munyaka directly (drmunyaka@eng.ucsd.edu).➘➘If you have other research-related problems, you may reach Dr. Imani Munyaka at drmunyaka@eng.ucsd.edu. If you have any questions concerning your rights as a research subject, you may contact the UC San Diego Office of IRB Administration at irb@ucsd.edu or 858-246-4777. You can download a copy of the form by clicking the link below or by emailing us at designstudyresearchers@gmail.com.<br><br>Copy of Consent {ADD THIS}<br>
QID111_QuestionText	Please select all of the statements you agree with.
QID111_Choice1	Roblox is not a safe place for children under 18
QID111_Choice2	I think parents need to monitor their child's behavior on Roblox
QID111_Choice3	Roblox is for children and adults
QID111_Choice4	Roblox is a safe place for children under 18
QID112_QuestionText	Imagine a friend comes to you and has expressed being concerned about their child being <b>financially scammed</b> on Roblox. They have asked you to share a link to information that would be helpful in identifying a solution for this problem. What link would you provide?
QID113_QuestionText	Imagine a friend comes to you and has expressed being concerned about their child being <b>antisocial</b> due to their playtime on Roblox. They have asked you to share a link to information that would be helpful in identifying a solution for this problem. What link would you provide?
QID114_QuestionText	Imagine a friend comes to you and has expressed being concerned about their child being exposed to <b>inappropriate content</b> on Roblox. They have asked you to share a link to information that would be helpful in identifying a solution for this problem. What link would you provide?
QID115_QuestionText	Imagine a friend comes to you and has expressed being concerned about their child being <b>contacted by adults</b> on Roblox. They have asked you to share a link to information that would be helpful in identifying a solution for this problem. What link would you provide?
QID116_QuestionText	Please take a few minutes (no more than 5) to review Roblox.com. In your opinion, which issues does Roblox address on their website.
QID116_Choice1	Click to write Choice 1
QID116_Choice2	Click to write Choice 2
QID116_Choice3	Click to write Choice 3
QID117_QuestionText	Please use the space below to provide any additional comments regarding the previous questions.
QID103_QuestionText	What is your job's official title?
QID106_QuestionText	What industry do you work in?
QID106_Choice1	Academia
QID106_Choice2	Industry
QID106_Choice3	Other
QID38_QuestionText	Please specify the gender with which you most closely identify.
QID38_Choice1	Male
QID38_Choice2	Female
QID38_Choice3	Non-binary
QID38_Choice4	Prefer not to say
QID38_Choice5	Prefer to self-describe
QID39_QuestionText	What is your age?
QID39_Choice1	18-22
QID39_Choice2	23-30
QID39_Choice3	31-40
QID39_Choice4	41-50
QID39_Choice5	51-60
QID39_Choice6	Over 60
QID39_Choice7	Prefer not to answer
QID40_QuestionText	Please specify your race/ethnicity
QID40_Choice1	White  (1)
QID40_Choice2	2. ➙Hispanic or Latino  (2)
QID40_Choice3	3. ➙Black or African American  (3)
QID40_Choice4	4. ➙Native American or American Indian  (4)
QID40_Choice5	5. ➙Asian  (5)
QID40_Choice6	6. ➙Native Hawaiian or Pacific Islander  (8)
QID40_Choice7	7. ➙Other  (6) ________________________________________________
QID40_Choice8	8.  Prefer not to answer  (7)
QID41_QuestionText	What is the highest degree or level of school you have completed?
QID41_Choice1	Some high school credit, no diploma or equivalent
QID41_Choice2	Less than high school degree  (8)
QID41_Choice3	High school graduate (high school diploma or equivalent including GED)  (9)
QID41_Choice4	Some college but no degree  (10)
QID41_Choice5	Associate's degree  (11)
QID41_Choice6	Bachelor's degree  (12)
QID41_Choice7	Advanced degree (e.g., Master's, doctorate)  (13)
QID41_Choice8	Prefer not to answer  (14)
QID107_QuestionText	Question Disability Questionnaire
QID107_Choice1	Are you deaf, or do you have serious difficulty hearing?
QID107_Choice2	 Are you blind,  visually impaired, or do you have serious difficulty seeing, even when wearing glasses?
QID107_Choice3	 Because of a physical, mental, or emotional condition, do you have serious difficulty concentrating, remembering, or making decisions?
QID107_Choice4	Do you have serious difficulty walking or climbing stairs? 
QID107_Choice5	Do you have difficulty dressing or bathing?
QID107_Choice6	Because of a physical, mental, or emotional condition, do you have difficulty doing errands alone such as visiting a doctor’s office or shopping? (15 years old or older)
QID105_QuestionText	Sexual Orientation
QID105_Choice1	Asexual
QID105_Choice2	Bisexual
QID105_Choice3	Pansexual
QID105_Choice4	Gay
QID105_Choice5	Heterosecual
QID105_Choice6	Lesbian
QID105_Choice7	Queer
QID105_Choice8	Prefer to self-describe
QID105_Choice9	Prefer not to answer
QID42_QuestionText	Which one of the following includes your total HOUSEHOLD income for last year, before taxes?
QID42_Choice1	Less than $10,000  (7)
QID42_Choice2	·   ➙$10,000 to under $20,000  (8)
QID42_Choice3	·   ➙$20,000 to under $30,000  (9)
QID42_Choice4	·   ➙$30,000 to under $40,000  (10)
QID42_Choice5	·   ➙$40,000 to under $50,000  (11)
QID42_Choice6	·   ➙$50,000 to under $65,000  (12)
QID42_Choice7	·   ➙$65,000 to under $80,000  (13)
QID42_Choice8	·   ➙$80,000 to under $100,000  (14)
QID42_Choice9	·   ➙$100,000 to under $125,000  (15)
QID42_Choice10	·   ➙$125,000 to under $150,000  (16)
QID42_Choice11	·   ➙$150,000 to under $200,000  (17)
QID42_Choice12	·   ➙$200,000 or more  (18)
QID42_Choice13	·    Prefer not to answer  (19)
QID102_QuestionText	Parental Status
QID102_Choice1	I have or had children that I currently support and/or raise by myself, with a partner, or as part of a team or family
QID102_Choice2	I do not have children that I currently support and/or raise by myself, with a partner, or as part of a team or family
QID102_Choice3	Prefer to self-describe (6)
QID102_Choice4	Prefer not to answer  (7)
QID108_QuestionText	Marital status
QID108_Choice1	Single
QID108_Choice2	Common Law Marriage
QID108_Choice3	Married
QID108_Choice4	Separated
QID108_Choice5	Divorced
QID108_Choice6	Widowed
QID108_Choice7	Legal
QID108_Choice8	Prefer to self-describe (6)
SurveyTitle	Qualtrics Survey | Qualtrics Experience Management
SurveyDescription	The most powerful, simple and trusted way to gather experience data. Start your journey to experience management and try a free account today.
